♪♪ One, two A one, two, three ♪♪
（警犬出生证明 露露）
（比利时牧羊犬 第75游骑兵团）
（收养契约 莱利罗利兹中士）
（训练结果：迅速 稳定可靠）
今天我走在常徘徊的街头
♪♪ Today I walked down The street I used to wander ♪♪
摇头 跟自己打赌
♪♪ Yeah, shook my hand And made myself a bet ♪♪
好多往事我已不记得
♪♪ There was all these things That I don't think I remember ♪♪
（敏捷度记分表）
我如此幸运
♪♪ Hey, how lucky Can one man get? ♪♪
（伊拉克 巴格达）
我把鞋擦亮 吊在后视镜
♪♪ I bronzed my shoes and I hun 'Em from a rearview mirror ♪♪
钦佩自己的矛盾与遗憾
♪♪ Bronzed admiration In a blind spot of regret ♪♪
好多往事我已不记得
♪♪ There was all these things That I don't think I remember ♪♪
（露露最爱的《实习医生》集数）
（游骑兵与警犬的义行）
我如此幸运
♪♪ Hey, how lucky Can one man get? ♪♪
（内有恶犬 哈哈）
（陆军游骑兵与警犬救援任务）
今天我走在常徘徊的街头
♪♪ Today I walked down The street I used to wander ♪♪
摇头 跟自己打赌
♪♪ Yeah, shook my hand And made myself a bet ♪♪
（永远是你的主人）
（临床评估：焦虑 对光敏感）
好多往事我已不记得
♪♪ There was all these things That I don't think I remember ♪♪
（退伍令或退役证明）
我如此幸运
♪♪ Hey, how lucky Can one man get? ♪♪
（你曾中弹 但这次更严重）（我仍内疚不已）
（你是勇士 也带来无私的爱） （你的兄弟 莱利）
我如此幸运
♪♪ Hey, how lucky Can one man get? ♪♪
（阿富汗巴格兰任务）
我如此幸运
♪♪ Hey, how lucky Can one man get? ♪♪
（你不仅仅是只狗）
（片名：逍遥上路）
-要干酪吗？-要
- You want cheese? - Sure.
生菜和西红柿？
Lettuce, tomato?
我要生菜 西红柿
Uh, let me get some lettuce, tomato,
和一些青椒
and let me get some of those peppers.
好
Done.
你傻了吗？
Yo, are you high?
我说青椒 不是黄瓜
I said peppers, not cucumbers.
抱歉 我搞错
Sorry, sir, my bad.
美乃滋和芥末酱？
Mayo, mustard?
美乃滋 还要
Uh, mayo, and, uh,
盐和胡椒 老兄
give me some of that salt and pepper, buddy.
全球安全中心你好
Black Canopy Global Security.
嗨 多莉 我是杰克森布里格
Hi, Dorith. This is Jackson Briggs.
请问我轮调巴基斯坦的进度
I was just checking on my status for the Pakistan rotation.
我想确认我的派驻
Um, just trying to sort my travel.
布里格先生 有脑损伤病史的士兵
Mr. Briggs, you know the agency can't send a soldier
不能派去战区
with a history of brain injuries to a war zone.
不 我有提供康复的医疗报告
No, no, I just got you guys a full, clean medical.
对 但你少了指挥官的担保
Yes, but we need your commanding officer to certify that.
我提醒募兵的人好多次了
Yeah, and I've told the recruiter, like, 12 times.
他们还无法提供
You know these guys. They're impossible to reach on deployment.
但快了 不如先跑报到流程
But it's coming. So let's just get the on-boarding process going
确定我的派驻
and, I don't know, get my travel sorted.
布里格先生 别为难我们
Mr. Briggs, you know we can't do that.
听着 各单位都抢着要我
Look, I got other agencies beating down my door,
所以...
so, look...
我无法等到明年才轮调
So, look, I can't wait till next year's rotation, okay?
没长官推荐就不能分发
And we can't staff you without that recommendation.
好吧 推荐期限到什么时候？
Okay, uh, when do I need to have it by?
轮调申请只到下周三
The rotation closes next Wednesday.
好 等我的消息
All right, you'll hear from me.
-喂？-布里格 我是琼斯
- Hello. - Briggs, this is Jones.
嗨 上尉
Hey, Captain.
你在忙吗？
Are you in the middle of something?
不忙 请说
No, no, it's a good time.
我刚打去问外交安全申请的事
Yeah, no, I was calling about that diplomatic security application
正希望你能帮我
I was hoping you'd help me with.
我打来是想通知罗利兹的事
Look, I'm calling about Rodriguez.
他昨晚去世了
He passed away last night.
你可能有听说
Stop me if you already heard this.
不会吧
No.
我没听说
No, I didn't hear.
请节哀
I'm sorry, Briggs.
我们会在老地方办告别式
We're all going to Patton Barracks to say goodbye to him.
-什么时候？-明晚
- When? - Tomorrow night.
好
All right.
-布里格？ -是 我会到场
- Briggs? - Yeah, I'll be there.
罗利兹中士是个传奇人物
Sergeant Rodriguez was a legend
他从不放弃
who never quit.
他发光发亮 令人难忘
He burned bright and then he burned in.
敬空降游骑兵
Airborne Ranger in the sky.
看靴子就知道他是空降游骑兵
You can tell an Airborne Ranger by his boots!
靴子万岁
By his boots!
荣耀 胜利
♪♪ Glorious! Victorious! ♪♪
咱们四人再来一桶啤酒 颂赞上帝
♪♪ Ay! One keg of beer For the four of us! ♪♪
（刮刮乐）
（烧烤酒吧）
我只要他打去说我没问题
Just need you to call and just be like, "He's good."
-不会吧 -小事一桩
- No. - That's it.
我想赚钱
I'm trying to get some money.
我只是想赚钱
I'm trying to get some money, that's it.
年薪20万就够了
200K a year,
你想派瑞会帮我打电话吗？
that's all I want. Just, like, make the call for me.
真希望我能帮忙
Yeah, I wish I had that power,
可惜我是小咖
but your boy's still an E-6, so...
没人鸟我
that's not happening.
我喜欢他 闭嘴啦
I love him. You shut your mouth.
别扯我后腿就好
You shut your mouth when you talk about him.
祝好运 兄弟
Good luck, brother.
戒律 戒律
Taboo! Taboo!
起来 基南 快点
Get up, Kiernan. Come on.
-噢 不 -你要惹毛我了
- Oh, no. - You're pissing me off.
-走吧 -振作点
- Let's go. - Come on. Hey, hey, hey.
我们会搞定 我们会搞定
Hey, hey, figure it out. Figure it out.
布里格 别烦我了
Okay, Briggs, get on with it.
-什么？-你心知肚明
- What? - You know what.
谁叫你
Hey, you're the one who's
不接电话又不回简讯
screening my calls and ghosting my texts, sir.
要是你马子早就爆气了
Like, what's a girl supposed to think?
都怪有人不识相
He's supposed to get the hint.
「嗨 我是琼斯上尉」
"Hi, it's Captain Jones
「我代表布里格上士来电」
calling on behalf of Staff Sergeant Briggs.
「他是个狠角色」
He's a total badass,
「他准备好了 可以上工」
he's squared away, good to go."
你帮50个士兵打过这通电话
You made that call for 50 other soldiers.
对 医生可没诊断
Yeah, who haven't been flagged for TBIs.
他们脑受损
Take it up with the doctors, not me.
拜托 巴瑞只剩一只手
Look, Bear's got half a hand.
你的屁股里也积了一堆炮弹碎片
You got a, like a chunk of shrapnel stuck in your tramp stamp.
基南连名字都记不得
Kiernan can barely remember his name.
-闭嘴啦 -停车场放眼望去
- Shut your mouth. - There's a hundred concussions
大家都有脑震荡
walking around this entire parking lot.
但你们还是照样冲
And it's not stopping y'all.
快进去
In, in.
我们的伤没有建档
Ours aren't on paper.
检查你的信 我有康复的医疗报告
Maybe check your email. I got a full, clean medical.
你花多少钱买的？
Yeah? How much you pay for that?
那不是重点
That's not the point.
开出你的条件吧
Sir, name it, what do you want? Tell me what you want.
抱歉 回家吧
I'm sorry, get home safe.
你要走了？
You're just gonna get in... Okay.
那我跪给你看
You want me to get the... All right, I'm getting the knee pads.
我跪给你看 求你了
I'm getting the knee pads, sir. Come on.
你要闪人了？
Are you really just gonna pull out right now?
你最好去拿把枪毙了我
Might as well just get the strap out of the center console
不让我归队
and put me down if I can't get back in the game,
就把我毙了吧
just go ahead and end it for me.
结束我的痛苦 无所谓
Just put me out of my misery, it's fine.
布里格 回家吧 这是命令
Briggs, get home safe. That's an order.
长官 你要去哪？长官
Sir, where are you goin'? Sir!
长官
Sir!
空降了
Airborne!
布里格上士还真是个狠角色
Staff Sergeant Briggs is a total badass, huh?
嗨 上尉
Oh, hey, Captain.
就猜到你还在
Figured I'd find you still here.
梳洗一下
Get yourself together.
30分钟后来部队找我
Come meet me in Battalion in 30.
你要帮我打电话了？
Does that mean you're gonna make the call?
上尉 大家都在说你坏话
Hey, Captain, all the guys talk shit about you,
但我就知道你是好人
but I always knew you had a heart of gold,
上尉好棒棒
and I was like, "Not my captain.
你不是烂人
No."
（刘易斯堡）
（刘易斯麦克乔德联合基地）
（宪兵）
-你好 -嗨
- What's up, man? - Howdy.
谢谢
Thank you.
证件过期了
It's expired, sir.
别这样
Oh, come on, man.
我进出这里像家一样
You know how many times I've been in and out of this gate with that?
你说啥？
Excuse me?
我看起来像恐怖分子吗？
Okay, think about it. What's the odds I'm ISIS?
先生 请下车
Step out of the vehicle, sir.
你要我下车？
You want me to step out of the vehicle...
-喂 -我很乐意
- Hey. - ...I'll happily...
他是游骑兵部队
He's with the Ranger battalion.
游骑兵很威吧
Ranger battalion.
证件早该作废了
You're required to dispose of this.
你说啥？什么？
What did you say? I'm sorry, what?
感谢你为国效力
Thank you for your service.
我会为祖国积极与敌作战
Energetically will I meet the enemies of my country!
我将在战场上击败敌人
I shall defeat them on the field of battle!
依靠良好的训练
For I am better trained.
全力攻敌
And will fight with all my might!
游骑兵誓死不屈
Surrender is not a Ranger word.
我绝不会舍弃倒下的战友
I'll never leave a fallen comrade...
我的停车位不能停
What? Y'all gave away my parking spot.
害我走好远
I had to walk all the way from the DFAC.
-继续保持 -你们要去哪？
- Keep pushing. - Where are y'all headed?
我们24小时内要降落在叙利亚
We're wheels down in Syria in 24 hours.
运输机正在装机
C-17 is loading up as we speak.
感谢长官
Look, sir, I really appreciate this,
我不会让你失望
I ain't gonna let you down.
为了归队我已经
I've been working the last three years
准备三年了
to get it straight for this job.
真中听
That's what I like to hear.
就说要当作举起你老妈
Kennelo, what did I say about using your mom's weights? Like...
我倒想练到能把到你妈
I'm trying to look good for your mom.
我只是建议
Well, I'm just trying to say, just...
用股四头肌
I don't know, more quads.
帮你生个弟弟
Gonna give you a baby brother.
你打算干嘛？
So what do you gotta do? Interview me or something
给我问话 确定我头壳没坏？
to make sure I've got a brain cell left, or...
对 之类的
Yeah, something like that.
一切你说了算 那好
Well, you say, "Jump," I say, "How high?"
等等 你的办公室不是这边？
Wait, isn't your office this way?
是又怎样
Sure is.
基南 莱利的遗物准备好了？
Riley's stuff just about ready, Kiernan?
快好了 长官
Just about, sir.
你还好吗？
You good, man?
还行 老样子
Yeah, man. It is what it is.
（《给战争一个机会》）
莱利确实值得敬重
Riley was about as solid as they come.
听说他超速撞树
Tell that to the tree he hit doin' 120.
基南 走吧
All right, Kiernan, let's go, come on.
（露露 《爱自己》）
狗要怎么处理？
What's gonna happen to his dog?
我就等你这句话
Thought you'd never ask.
周日家属要在诺加利斯举办葬礼
Family funeral's Sunday outside of Nogales.
她是贵宾
She's the guest of honor.
有够天才
Oh, that's... That's a genius idea.
希望她不会先把人给吃了
I hope she doesn't eat everybody first.
那就要看你了
Well, that part will be up to you.
等等 啥？
Wait, wait, what?
准备好了？拼了
Ready? Get it!
我们昨晚送走莱利的遗体
We sent Riley's body off late last night.
今早他母亲来电
And his mother called this morning.
她要他的爱犬出席葬礼
She wants his hero dog at the funeral.
你要我搭飞机把狗送到亚利桑那州？
Sir, are you asking me to fly a damn dog to Arizona?
不 是开车送游骑犬到亚利桑那州
No, I'm asking you to drive a Ranger to Arizona.
她不肯坐飞机
She refuses to fly.
她为什么不跟你们派驻？
Why ain't she deploying with you?
她不和任何人合作 一会很乖
Won't work with anyone. One minute she's good,
一会把三个人咬成重伤
the next minute, she's sending three guys to the ER.
你们受伤后 莱利顾着她
Riley kept trying after you guys got blown up,
但她现在没用了
but she's gone all the way.
莱利在超速撞树前
Maybe Riley should have thought of that
早该考虑到
before he broke the speed of sound into a tree.
游骑兵老爱寻死
Yeah, well, Rangers find a way to die.
等等 让我搞清楚
Hold on, let me get this straight,
要是我答应 你就会打电话
so I agree to do this, and you're gonna call Black Canopy
加速我的申请？
and get my packet pushed.
你答应 我就打电话 别搞砸
You do this, and then I make the call, no screw-ups,
不准添麻烦
nothing gets back to me.
完事后去白沙基地
After the service, you drop off on base down at White Sands,
他们会处理后续
they'll handle the rest.
白沙？要给她安乐死？
White Sands? So they're just gonna put her down anyway.
没有饲主或警局会疯到想收养她
There's not a handler or a PD crazy enough to adopt her up.
我们也不乐见 但没辙
Doesn't make us feel warm and fuzzy inside. Just is what it is.
那我把她放生 你打电话
How about I disappear her ass, you make the call,
咱们皆大欢喜 好主意吧
and we both go on with our lives? How about that?
你完成任务 我就会挺你
You stick your neck out for Battalion, I'll stick mine out for you.
-不要拉倒 -长官
- Take it or leave it. - Sir...
准备来接你的暴冲狗了？
Ready to pick up your furry flash-bang?
我是奉命而来
That's what I'm told, man.
听好 这只狗转性了
Here's the deal, Briggs, this isn't the same dog you served with,
战争经历让她变得好斗
she's got every combat trigger in the book.
看紧她 别带她到公共场合
So you keep her secured and you don't take her out in public.
懂吗？
We clear?
好
All right.
有人问 就说要送她去复健
If anyone asks, say she's on her way to rehabilitation.
要我解开她吗？
Hey, do you want me to leash her up for you?
我自己动手
No, let's just get this over with.
好吧
All right.
你好 狗狗
What's up, dog?
记得我吗？
You remember me?
你几年前最爱拿我来磨牙了
Your favorite chew toy from 2015.
没印象？
Huh?
我和你要上路了
Me and you are gonna go on a little road trip.
超过1500英里
Fifteen hundred miles.
你爹地会在天上保佑我们
Just to act like your daddy's looking down on us from above.
好 我要解开你了
All right, I'm gonna leash you up.
好吗
All right?
冷静 别激动
Be cool. Easy.
冷静
Easy.
你真的认命了？
You really did give up, huh?
你们怕什么？她很乖啊
What are y'all so scared of? She's milding out big-time.
住手
Stop!
不要
Enough!
老兄 忘了提醒你别碰她耳朵
Hey, man, I forgot to tell you not to touch her on the ears, man.
我漏掉重点
I left that part out.
她戒了抗忧郁药
Hey, we weaned her off the Prozac,
有时会喜怒无常
so she might get moody from time to time.
嘴套一次只能戴2小时
Her muzzle can only stay on
不然她会热衰竭
for about two hours at a time or she'll overheat.
记得食物里要放水
Make sure you put water in her food,
还有别碰她的耳朵
and as you know, don't touch her ears.
最后就是她的纪录本
Other than that, here's your Bible.
-旅途愉快 -回头见 基南
- Have a good trip. - See you, Trent.
谢谢长官
Thank you, sir.
罗利兹背包里的遗物都还给家属
All the belongings in Sergeant Rodriguez's backpack go to his family.
他们想要他的军服陪葬
They want his uniform at the funeral.
本子则是露露的
The "I Love Me" book, that stays with Lulu.
遇到麻烦时 翻翻她的信息
If you have any trouble, all her info's in there.
我们不会去太久
I'm not gonna be out there long enough.
-嘿 -游骑兵做先锋
- Hey. - Rangers lead the way, sir.
勇往直前
All the way.
-保重 -兄弟
- Good luck. - All right, boys.
看来布里格终于把到妹了
Looks like Briggs finally got a girl.
（奥勒冈州真奇怪）
再怎么努力也回不到水里
♪♪ Can't try much harder To get back to water ♪♪
回去会更热 回到水里
♪♪ Gonna get back hotter Get back, get back to water ♪♪
我是多莉
This is Dorith.
多莉 又是我杰克森布里格
Hey, Dorith, this is Jackson Briggs again.
我打来跟你们说
I was just calling to let you guys know
我只坐商务舱
that I only fly business class
飞去中东国家
to countries with names that end in "stan."
我们还没收到你的推荐
Sir, we're still missing your recommendation.
你讲到重点
Uh, look, it's actually what I was callin' about.
周一的一大早
So, first thing Monday morning, uh,
第二游骑兵部队琼斯上尉
you'll be getting a call from Captain Luke Jones
会打给你
from Second Ranger Battalion.
只要周三前你的上尉打来
If we hear from your captain before Wednesday,
我就会通知区安官安排你的轮调
I'll let the RSO know to expect you on rotation.
女士 感谢协助
Yes, ma'am, I'm very, very happy to be working with...
我听不清楚
Yes, sir, I can't hear you...
女士 感激不尽
Yes, ma'am, yes, ma'am, thank you so much. I... Okay.
怎么了？
What?
你有什么毛病啦
What is your deal, man?
拜托
Come on.
椅子上都是你的口水
You're just slobbering all over my seat.
别发疯
Maybe just take the crazy down.
冷静一点
Just like one notch.
也许我们能相处愉快
Just one notch, that's it, and maybe we could get along.
这样也许我们就能开心玩
And if we get along, maybe we could even have some fun
好好和莱利道别
and send Riley off right.
听起来不赖吧 狗狗
Doesn't that sound nice, dog?
你只有我了
I'm all you got, I'm it.
就是这样 你没得选
It's just me.
说实话 我也不想整天给你戴嘴套
Believe it or not, I don't wanna keep you all muzzled up 24/7.
我真的不想
I really don't.
还有 我也不想直接
And to be honest, I don't wanna drive
开到荒凉的沙漠小镇
straight to some dry-ass desert town
坐在汽车旅馆干瞪着墙五天
and just sit in a motel and stare at a wall for five days
枯等他的葬礼
waiting for his funeral.
对吧？
Do you?
别吵了行不行 好啦
Come on, man. Okay, okay, fine, fine, fine, fine.
我要脱下嘴套了
All right. So I gotta take your muzzle off,
敢咬我
but if you bite me,
你就给我整路戴着
I'm gonna leave it on all the way to Arizona.
别暴走
So be chill,
好吗 很好
all right? That's great.
还记得以前我们一起出任务的日子
Just remember all those times
破门而入 赶尽杀绝
we had fun kicking in doors, getting our murder on.
放轻松 我不是坏人
Relax, I'm not the bad guy.
冷静 别咬我的帅脸
Easy. Do not bite me in the face, all right?
我要靠近了
I'm gonna reach up,
我不会碰到你的耳朵
I'm not gonna touch your ears, or near your ears.
我不会碰
All right, I'm not touchin' that, I'm not touchin' that.
我们好棒棒
All right, all right. We're good, we're good.
你看我们搞定了
Okay, look at that. We did it, we did it.
没事 搞定了
We did it.
好了
All right.
不要 够啰
Hey, no, no, stop!
够了 冷静啦
Stop it. Hey, hey, chill out.
算了 给我待在里面
Fine, fine. Stay in there then.
待在里面 自己玩
Stay in there, have fun.
掰 疯狗
Bye, crazy town.
（橡树靶场）
你要撇尿吗？
Hey, you ready to go to the shitters?
嘿！不行
Hey! No, no, no. No!
别这样
No!
我要宰了你 老天
I'm gonna kill you. Oh, my...
不行 可恶
No! Oh, my God!
你给我待着
You just stay right there!
（过敏药）
我原本想让你在路上开心一下
You know, I was gonna let you have a little bit of fun on this trip.
让你又跑又跳
I was gonna let you run and frolic,
闻闻一些屁眼 想得美
you know, sniff some buttholes and all that, but no,
他们说的没错 你是个恶魔
turns out they are right, you're just a demon.
大恶魔
You're just a demon!
好 最后道歉机会
All right, last chance to apologize.
不要？
No?
那晚安了 笨狗
All right, fine. Night-night, bitch.
在丛林中 伟大的丛林
♪♪ In the jungle The mighty jungle ♪♪
今晚狮子睡着了
♪♪ The lion sleeps tonight ♪♪
怎么啦
Oh, what's happening?
有点困了？
You're gettin' a little sleepy back there?
还是累了？
Someone gettin' a little tired, tired?
今年的过敏季节真严重
Oh, allergy season is brutal this year.
你以前不是很猛很厉害吗？
Man, you used to be a legend. Not no more, huh?
现在只能在我面前打盹
You're just falling asleep on me.
等等 你说什么？
Wait, what'd you say?
「爹地该去喝啤酒」 说的对
Oh! Daddy should go out and get some beers, you're right.
我就让你瞇一下
Let you get a little shut-eye. Okay, I'll do that.
你真贴心 又说对了
That's really nice of you. You're right, too,
哥很久没打炮
I haven't been laid in a while.
也许没你久 但那不是重点
Maybe not as long as you but that's not the point.
我们同病相怜 保密喔
Still sad, and we'll keep that a secret.
好欸 波特兰 去爽啰
All right, Portlandia, let's turn it up.
（奥勒冈州 波特兰市）
抱歉 这里没有转基因生物啤酒
Hey, sorry, man. No GMOs here,
只有生物动力微酿啤酒
only bio-dynamic microbrew.
酷喔 我不用 这是什么？
Cool, I don't want that. What's this?
女士 你喝什么？
What're you... Ma'am, what're you having?
美格威士忌
Maker's.
美格再两杯 谢谢
Can we get two more of those, please?
你要直接喝还是…
You want me to tease it, or add to it?
直接倒在杯子里就好
Please don't tease it, just Maker's in a glass.
我们兄弟都
Look, all I'm saying is every single one of those kids
顺利返乡
got out of the compound all right.
我们不是英雄 只是尽忠职守
We're not heroes. We just do our jobs.
你根本不必在外排队
I mean, you don't have to wait in this line, you know?
只要戴上虚拟现实装置
You just pop on that VR headset, and boom,
就会立马来到地表最屌的酒吧
you're at the illest bar on Earth,
遇到我这种夯哥
hanging with guys like me.
那怎么喝到真正的啤酒？
How do you get to the actual beers, though?
虚拟啤酒 那样才正点
Virtual beers, bro. That's the beauty of it.
你一定很喜欢
'Cause you must be, like,
听民歌吧？
just the biggest Billy Ray Cyrus fan of all time.
我称得上民歌的铁粉
Well, I am actually a huge country fan.
我痛恨那些仇女
It's just a little hard for me to get behind the
恐同的人
toxic masculinity, you know.
讲中我心里的话
Yeah, that's exactly what I was saying. Yeah.
你什么时候发现
So at what point did you realize
自己被石油公司利用？
that you were just a pawn for big oil?
企业大亨展开生态
Just body bags carrying out ecological genocide
集体屠杀
for the corporate elite.
那些石油大亨
All these big oil fat cats,
自以为掌控这里
they think that they own this place.
自以为掌控大地
They think they own Mother Earth,
谁都不能霸占大地
but no one owns Mother Earth,
我这辈子每天都要对抗他们
and I'm gonna fight against them every day for the rest of my life
我可不想看到鸭子在油上游泳
because it's just not 'cause I don't wanna see those ducks in the goo.
听着 邀请50个
Look, and if you invite 50
IG朋友就半价
of your Instagram friends, you get half off.
-我有什么好处？酷喔 -我请喝酒
- What does this get me? Cool. - Free drink. On me.
绝对不能
No, no, no, no version of you
让女生请客 我买单
ever paying my bill. Please, no chance.
要我待会过来吗？
Would you like me to come right back?
不用了
No, we're good, I promise.
不能让她掏钱
Her money is no good here.
我来就好
I got it.
今晚我对自己说 你一定很爱
Tonight, I said to myself, you're gonna love this,
我说「你会遇到建筑工人或军人」
I said, "You will meet a construction worker or a soldier."
-这可妙了 -或是
- That's interesting. - Or, I don't know,
没有白人优越感的人
any man without a white savior complex.
祝好运
Good luck.
等等 什么？
Wait, what?
你最好去看精神科
I hope that you get the help that you need.
-感谢请客 -别走 听着
- Thanks for the drink. - No, no. Look, look,
听着 我被塔利班射杀耶
look, hey, I've been trapped by the Taliban.
我们走吧
We gotta get outta here
这里的妹子
because you are about the only woman in this entire city
都没你好聊
that I would actually like to have a conversation with.
我们和好吧
Here, this is a peace offering.
你冷静 我就会冷静 来
Be chill, and I'll be chill with you. Here.
我也不想对你下药
Look, I didn't want to drug you.
谁叫你咬烂我椅子 说真的
You didn't have to eat my seats, that's all I'm saying.
我们能当朋友 我只是以牙还牙
We can be friends, but this is gonna be an eye for an eye.
你要和好？
Are we gonna be cool?
还是继续跟我斗？
Or do we need to have another meeting of the mind?
随便 你不信我？
Fine, you don't wanna trust me, fine.
我懒得鸟你
I don't even care.
反正我也不信任你
I definitely don't trust you, so whatever.
那是比利时牧羊犬？
Is that a Belgian Mal?
是啊
Uh, yeah. Yeah, it is.
-她好漂亮 -甜心
- She's beautiful. - Hi, sweet girl.
-你是搜救犬？-算吧
- Are you a rescue? - Uh, sort of.
她喜欢狗狗同伴吗？
Does she like other dogs?
算了
No, um, no, no.
其实她现在有点烦闷
Actually she's, um, she's a little sad right now.
她有点烦闷
She's... She's, um, grieving.
她失去了伙伴
She lost her best friend.
好惨 甜心
Oh, no, sweetheart.
这两个小可爱叫什么名字？
I know. Who are... Who are these little cuties?
-这是露西 -这是玛吉
- Oh, this is Lucy. - This is Maggie.
她们好可爱
Aw, they're so cute.
-是西施犬 -太棒了
- They're Shih Tzus. - They're great.
我爱西施犬
Oh, I love Shih Tzus.
-给你 -谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
干杯
Cheers.
我差点放弃这城市 幸好遇到你们
I was about to give up on this city before I met y'all.
波特兰不是老少咸宜
Well, Portland's not for everybody.
谁知道 我开始喜欢这里了
I don't know, it's growin' on me.
又不是每天能遇到两个「植物音乐家」正妹
It's not every day you meet two plant musician ladies.
我们其实是坦陀罗教徒
We're actually Tantrikas.Um...
好
Okay.
我们有时也会充当入神圆舞的DJ
We DJ ecstatic dance circles sometimes, though.
像瑜伽吗？
That's sick. Is that, like... That's like yoga?
我做过瑜伽 但我超逊的
I've done yoga. But I'm horrible at it.
我们会唤醒能量帮人治疗
We help heal people by moving blocked energy
让人体验到完整的性愉悦
so they can experience the full potential of sexual pleasure.
原来你们会唤醒能量
So you just move the energy for...
那我回车上拿钱
Hell, yeah. I can... I mean, I got cash in the truck, I think.
别误会
Oh, no, no.
吸引力只需真心诚意
No, the attraction is completely genuine.
好神奇
Ah. I mean...
只要你能感受到那股流动
As long as it's in the flow for you.
我不用啦
No, I'm good.
开玩笑的
Kidding.
我的流动超猛
I'm so in... I'm so in the flow.
赞 我超爱脉轮这种玩意
Great, I love some chakrastuff.
你们在呼麻吗？
Do we smoke that or...
-不是 -不是吗
- No. - No?
这太屌了
This is... This is rad.
你的宝贝狗想要进来吗？
Does your baby wanna come in?
不必 她能自得其乐
Nope, she's good, she's just happy.
她叫得很开心
She's a happy... That's a happy bark.
为我打气
She's just letting me know.
现在我们的心是什么状态？
How are our hearts in this moment?
我的心是…
Mmm, my heart is, um...
圆满的 我找到了新工作
just full and it's like... I mean, I got a new job.
情况好转了
Yeah, uh, things are really looking up.
我感觉很充实
I just feel solid. I feel solid over here,
准备前进
I'm ready to go.
-我还没到那个阶段 -好
- Um, I'm not quite there yet. - Okay.
好的
Okay.
贝拉 也许欢喜佛能转换更多能量
But maybe yab-yum would help move some prana.
我的心正需要能量
This is what my heart needed.
来吧
Yeah, let's go.
感觉很棒吧？
So good, right?
是啊
All right.
我能脱下你的上衣吗？
May I have permission to remove your shirt?
废话 我自己脱
Hell, ye... I'm gonna remove it for you.
还好吗？
Hey, hey, hey. What's going on?
很闷吗？
Why are you so upset?
可怜鬼
Oh, poor baby.
我的佛陀啊
Oh, my Buddha.
没事 只是战伤
Oh, no, no. That's, like, some old army shit.
小菜一碟
Don't worry about that.
-你们有疤痕吗？-怎么受伤的？
- You guys... - What's this from?
不记得了 但大疤痕是自动步枪
I don't know. That one is... The big one's an AK round.
你的身体很痛苦 很遗憾
Your body is in so much pain. I'm so sorry, we had no idea.
不要紧
No, no, look, it's fine.
我能脱掉你的上衣吗？
It's fine. Do I have permission to remove your shirt?
我想照顾你的心
'Cause I wanna take care of your heart.
怪不得我们会互相吸引
This is why we were drawn together.
有够混蛋
What an asshole.
怎样？
What?
按住我的手
Place my hand...
让你的痛苦来引导
wherever your pain guides it.
没问题
Yeah, I can do that.
好主意 从这里开始吧
I like this plan. Why don't we start here?
我要放狗了
Let's get you out of here.
不好意思
I'm sorry, um...
抱歉
I'm sorry. I can't, uh,
-狗狗让我分心了 -我去看一下她
- I can't hold this pace. - I'll go check on her,
我去看一下她 好吗
how about that? I'll go check on her. Just...
你待着 保持好能量
You stay right there and you just keep the energy.
嘿！
Hey!
嘿！你在干嘛？
Hey! What are you doing?
解放受虐的动物
Freeing that abused animal.
警告你 扔石头是自找苦吃
You throw that rock and we're about to see who's abused.
少在那边用暴力威胁 乡巴佬
Of course you threaten violence, you redneck!
拿石头的人是你
Red... You're the one with the rock, man.
放下走人
Just put it down and walk away.
-我们相安无事 -你最好搞清楚 动物也是人
- I promise you... - Animals are people, too.
-好的 -快放她出来
- Okay... - Let her out now or I will.
-你理解... -都还好吗？
- You understand... - Are you okay?
-怎么回事？-没啥大不了
- What's going on? - Oh, no. It's no big deal.
有个善心人士过来确定狗…
He's just a nice man, came over to make sure the dog...
狗狗回来 走开
Hey! Dog, get back here!
不要
No!
快停 别咬
Stop! Let go! No!
-走开 -听话
- No! - Get it off.
-放开 -快回来
- Heel! - Release!
死笨狗 要死啦
Come on. All right. Come on. Let go!
-够了 你要干嘛？-我要报警了
- Stop it. - I'm callin' the cops.
我超讨厌你的
You... Son of a...
你毁了我3P的大好机会
All right, now, you ruined an epic threesome.
回来
No. Hey! Ah!
笨狗
Bitch!
你们要去哪？
Where are you guys going?
那我的痛苦呢？
What about... What about my pain?
上车啦
God, just get in the car.
（奥勒冈州感谢您 欢迎再度莅临）
你到底怎么了 狗狗？
Whatever happened to you, dog, huh?
记得莫瑞过世时 莱利逼我们…
Remember when Maretti died?
看15小时的《实习医生》吗？
Riley made us watch, like, 15 hours of Grey's Anatomy.
大家随地坐着
Everybody was sitting around and then you just came around
你把头凑过来蹭每个人
with your fat head, nuzzling everybody,
装可爱 逗大家笑
being all cute, making everybody laugh.
那只可爱狗狗去哪了？
Whatever happened to that dog, huh?
军队容不下累赘
The army has no place for liabilities
你变累赘了
and that's all you are now.
懂吧 这就是你和我的不同
See, you know, that's the difference between you and I, though.
你知道吗
You know that?
脑科医生说我这辈子都会残疾
Those brain doctors said I'd be on disability for the rest of my life.
你爸不同
Not your dad, though.
他没被问话就回去了
Your dad, they just sent back with no questions asked.
他们说我会视力模糊
They said I'd never see straight,
头痛 遇到压力会
I'd have headaches and if I got stressed out,
癫痫发作 死掉什么鬼的
that I'd have seizures and die or some bullshit like that,
但你没看到我癫痫发作变废人吧？
but you don't see some little seizure stopping me, do you?
倒是你老是闯祸
But you, on the other hand, look, if you don't want it,
你无药可救了
ain't no cure for that shit.
像你和我这种咖 不努力就死定了
People like me and you are better off just being all in or all out.
我可不想跟你一样
I just wouldn't want some bullshit-ass injection,
被安乐死
like you're going to have.
反正你没得选
I mean, it's not like you've got a choice in the matter,
也死得不光荣
but it's just not a warrior's death.
要是我会偷一架螺旋桨飞机
I'd probably steal a prop plane
飞向高空
and fly that bitch right into the sun
直到引擎挂掉
till the engines froze out.
然后跳机
And then I'd swan dive right out of the cockpit
像007一样帅
and laugh my ass all the way to Valhalla.
帮帮忙 别发牢骚了
Hey, come on, man, stop the whining.
你听起来像爱哭夭的吉娃娃
You sound like a whiney-ass chihuahua.
糟了 该死
Oh, shit. Okay. Hey, hey, hey!
回来
Hey! No, no, no!
不要 回来
No, no!
不要 过来
Hey, look. No, no, no, no. Come here.
狗狗
Hey, dog!
狗狗 过来 不要
Dog, come here. No!
过来
Come here!
狗狗
Hey, dog!
Dog!
狗狗
Hey, dog!
过来
Hey, come!
糟了
Oh, shit.
不会吧 狗狗 我们不该进来
No, no, no, no, no. Dog, we're not supposed to be in here.
快走
Let's go.
有人吗？
Hello?
有人在吗？
过来
Come!
狗狗？
Dog?
出来
Come on.
嘿！
Hey!
老天 有没有搞错
Oh, shit. You've gotta be kidding me.
狗狗？
Dog!
嘿 狗狗
Hey, dog!
有人吗？
Hello?
有没有人？
Hello!
大块头
Hey, big fella.
你给我下什么药？镇静剂？
Hey, what did you hit me with, man? Horse tranq?
还真猛
This is pretty good.
该招供了
Time for you to start squealing.
你有看到一只棕色的狗吗？
Hey, have you seen a dog? She's brown,
跑得很快 眼神很凶
she's, like, running around, I don't know, with crazy eyes, huh?
是谁派你来的？
Tell me who you work for.
听着
Okay, look,
你绝对认错人了
I'm obviously not who you think I am.
我知道你是什么来历
I know who the hell you are.
你以为老子没遇过突击部队？
Think you're the first commando they sent up here?
想抢走我的大麻？
Take my strains?
老头 除非你想
Look, old man, unless you're willing to
自找罪受
walk this till the end of the road,
我强烈建议你
I highly suggest you cut me loose
把我松绑让我找回狗
and let me go find my damn dog.
你有5分钟解释
You got five minutes to clear your head,
不然就会步上她的后尘
or you can join her ass.
赞啦
Hell, yeah.
你不知道我的能耐
Who the hell you think you're talking to?
等着看
We'll see about that.
王八蛋
Bitch!
忍无可忍 有够白目
Oh, that is... That's bullshit.
狗狗 快过来
Dog, come here, come here.
狗狗 过来
Now! Come here!
要走了
Come here!
葛斯 他醒了吗？
Gus, is he awake yet?
清醒了 绑在马房里
Wide awake. He's zip-tied in the barn.
绑？天啊
Zip-tied? Oh, my God.
你对他做了什么？
What the hell did you do to him?
我给他下药 骗说杀了他的狗
Some shit. I told him I killed his dog.
你哪里懂审问
Gus, what do you know about interrogation?
你拒绝服兵役耶
You were a conscientious objector.
称赞人家一下嘛
How about a little damn appreciation?
就叫你别哈太多草
I told you not to hit those edibles so hard.
毒枭？你太疑神疑鬼了
Cartel? You paranoid maniac.
跟他说你是
Tell him you're crazy, I'm not...
秀逗没胆的老笨蛋
a scared old fool who needs heavy therapy.
向他道歉
Just tell him you're sorry.
我给他注射镇静剂
I shot him with a tranquilizer.
-我不在乎 -我把他推到粪土
- I don't care what you did. - I pushed him...
别激怒了这小可爱
Now you're making me upset this little nugget.
这毛小孩真乖
This perfect noodle...
听着 我们逃走吧
Listen, let's get the hell out of here.
坐着 我想看看你的小脚掌
'Cause I wanna look at your little, little paw.
你好乖
You're so good.
超乖的
So good.
真是个小可爱
What a little nugget.
-老公 -妈呀 我…
- Honey... - Look, Jesus, I...
闭嘴
Shut up.
坐下
Sit down.
你怎么让她听话的？
How'd you make her eat out of your hand?
我没干嘛
I didn't make her do anything.
只是对她说话而已
I just talked to her.
对了 你尽管教训
By the way, you can do anything you like
我的白痴老公
with my idiot husband.
葛斯 道歉
Gus, apologize.
抱歉 都是我的错
Sorry, dude. My bad, my bad.
她只是个毛小孩
Hmm, see, she's just a noodle.
又很懂事
She just needs some good...
我要碰你的小脚掌了
I'm just going to touch her little, little paw.
她会没事吧？
Is she gonna be okay?
我担心她的腿断了
Well, I'm worried she may have broken her foot,
但我会尽力
but I'm gonna try my best.
请问 她叫什么名字？
You need to give, um... What is her name?
露露
Lulu.
露露和我需要空间
Lulu and I some space.
这样吧
So, um, here.
葛斯 帮点忙
Come on. Gus, make yourself useful
给他干净衣服
and get this man some clean clothes
他闻起来一身屎味
because he's really smelling strongly of Boris and his friends.
吃点糖果 交个朋友
So here, take some homemade edibles. Go make friends, okay?
葛斯 快点 别发楞 出去
Guys, come on, stop it. Get outside.
听你唬烂 用鞋带就能搞定
You can't tell me that you did this with a damn shoestring.
破坏塑性就简单了
You just gotta compromise the plastic. That's it.
听着 我搞园艺的功夫比绑人强多了
Listen, I'm a lot better at permaculture than I am tying dudes up.
我想知道我那时有多接近⋯
I need to know, man, how close was I to...
-死亡？ -对
- Dying? - Yeah.
挺接近的
Pretty... Pretty close, actually.
我差点用斧头劈开你的头
I almost put an axe in the back of your head.
这大麻棒棒糖真屌
This is... Well done.
是不是？
Yeah, right? Right?
真高兴你是爱狗人士
I'm just glad you love that dog so much.
我不爱狗 那根本不是我的狗
I don't love that dog. It's not even my dog.
加油 用力
Come on, get on your back.
用力 你行的
Get on your back, you can do it.
-加油 -那是谁的狗？
- Come on. - Whose damn dog is it?
看到没？
Look, you see that?
-看到没？-赞啦
- You see this? - Yeah.
他们教狗追踪敌人
This is how they teach them to attract the enemy.
狗在一英里外就能闻到敌人的衣服
They can smell their clothes from, like, a mile off.
这两人死了？
Is this two dead dudes?
对 那里有两个塔利班
Yeah. Those are... That's two Taliban,
大麻农
uh, dope farmers right there.
别惊讶
Oh, don't look all shocked, man.
这是战争 那里可没有独角兽和美女
It's war. It's not all unicorns and rainbow vaginas out there, right?
靠 我好嗨
Yeah, I bet.
对了 为什么这本叫《爱自己》？
So why do they call it I Love Me book?
不知道 但军方要
I don't know. Uh, but in the army,
每个人都有一本
they just, they make us all keep one.
要我们记录每个细节
They make us put every single, last stupid detail in.
（露露首次驻外 巴格达战区）
露露的精选 是她最爱的音乐吧？
So, Lulu's greatest hits. This is like...
Like her music. Like, music she...
差多了 是另一种精选
No, no, no, no, no. It's the other greatest hits, you know.
她执行任务的影片
Like, it's her bodycam footage.
老天 我不想看
Oh, Jesus. It's the... kinda... Yeah, I'll pass.
让我搞清楚
So let me get this right, man.
这只狗立下大功
So, like, the dog did all this, man.
他们却要把她安乐死？
I mean, they're just going to put her down?
这样讲太感伤了
Look, don't get all misty-eyed on me, big man.
话不是这样讲
Like, it's... It's not like that.
那只狗完成了她的使命
That dog did exactly what she was born to do,
也就是活出传奇的人生
and that was to live a legendary life.
她达标了
And she did it.
还有什么？
What the hell is this here?
「亲爱的露露」
"Dear Lulu,
「我无法想象没遇到你会变怎样」
I can hardly imagine life before I knew you.
「你生来是只愤怒的野兽或是…」
Did you come into this world a beast of fury, or were you just..."
等等 那是啥？让我看
What was that? What was that?
看来他写了信
He wrote... It's like written up on top right there.
有几封
There's a couple of 'em,
很像诗或情书
like poems or love letters, or something.
罗利兹几乎不识字
Rodriguez could barely spell.
更不可能作诗
I mean, he definitely can't rhyme.
我懂了
I know what this is. This is...
脑受损时
So when you have a brain injury,
会被送去看脑科医生
you basically get sent to these brain doctors.
他们研究你 让你
And then they study you, and they make you draw
又写又画之类的鬼艺术治疗
and write and do all this art therapy bullshit.
没人当一回事
Nobody really takes it serious.
-靠 -哇塞
- Shit! - Oh!
狗狗
Dog!
你痊愈了
You're okay. Hey.
看她跑来跑去
Look at her. She's running around.
只是一小根铁丝
Yeah. There was just a little piece of barbed wire
刺进她的脚掌
just lodged way up in her paw.
我消毒止血了
I sterilized it and stopped the bleeding.
没看过这么强壮的狗
Never seen a dog so strong.
谢谢 感激不尽
Thank you. Thank you so much.
她还跟我产生感应
Also, she did offer me a transmission.
-悟性很高 -感应？
- If you feel called. - Transmission?
对 她的命中率很高
Yeah, she bats about 350 on those.
用棒球来比喻
I mean, but, you know, if it was baseball,
她能进名人堂了
it'd be hall of fame numbers.
你们俩肯定是注定的缘分
You two are definitely karmically connected.
她一定是投胎来找你
She must have incarnated to find you.
我看到金字塔
I'm seeing pyramids.
古埃及
Ancient Egypt.
有个小女孩在玩
Now, a young girl, she's playing.
她好快乐
Oh, she's so happy.
露露喜欢小孩吗？
Does Lulu work with kids?
对 她爱死小孩了
Yeah. She loves kids. She loves 'em.
-她会猛舔小孩的脸 -不可思议
- And licks their faces right off. - Unbelievable.
那可能是…
I think it might be
你女儿
your daughter.
她有个中性的名字？
Does she have a boy's name?
-中性的名字？-珊米
- A boy's name? - Uh, Sam.
我女儿怎么了？
Um, what about my daughter?
露露让我连结到她
Well, Lulu, she's bringing her into my awareness.
她几岁了？
How old is she?
三岁
Uh, three.
专心在狗身上就好
Let's... Let's just keep it about the dog.
好
Okay.
我感到又冷又硬
I'm feeling cold. Hard, yes.
她渴望柔软的床
She's yearning for soft. Yes, a bed.
高级的床垫
A luxury mattress.
她说她没睡过像样的床
She says she's never slept in a nice bed before.
可以吗？
She asks if it's okay.
-她在问我？-好呀
- She's asking me that? - Mmm.
当然了
Okay, yeah, sure.
我好热 口干舌燥
Now I'm getting hot... Tongue... Taste.
她想吃印度菜？
Indian food she wants?
你别闹了
Are you kidding me?
-葛斯 -丑三
- Gus. - Strike three.
葛斯 你干嘛吐槽我？
Gus, why do you undermine me?
狗才不想吃印度菜
The damn dog don't want Indian food.
幸好我们没有误杀好人
I'm so happy we didn't have to kill those nice people.
否则我们
But I'm just saying, if we did,
肯定得挖超大的洞
you were definitely digging the bigger hole
葛斯超大只的
'cause Gus was massive.
对了 下次嗅到大麻别溜掉
And by the way, the next time you smell weed,
通知我 我们可以一起嗨
don't run away, just let me know, and we can go get it together.
不可以 不行
Hey, hey, hey! No, no!
（勿杀生）
干嘛啦 狗狗
Why, man? Hey, dog!
（礼物专卖店）
不行 不可以
No, no, no, no, no, no!
不行 别咬
Stop it! No, no!
这是我的独角兽
This is my unicorn.
不要 够了
No, no, no, no, no. Stop!
好啦 过来 小巴 过来 管好你的狗
Stop it. Okay, all right, come on, come on. Let's go.
走啦 抱歉
Let's go. Sorry, guys.
我是妮基 请留言
Hey, it's Niki. Leave a message.
你看什么？
What are you looking at?
少在那边哭
What you whining for?
都怪你我们才没处去
You're the whole reason we're up here.
苦中作乐吧
Get comfy.
今晚睡这里
That's where you're sleeping tonight.
想念你的狗笼？
You're missing your cage?
看 那里是恶魔岛
Look. It's Alcatraz, it's right there.
我们能参观一下
Just take a little tour.
不然把你丢在那里好了
You know, possibly just leave you there.
你只剩三天活在地球上
You only got about three more days left on this green Earth,
及时行乐 以免为时已晚
so you better speak now or forever hold your peace.
听着 想睡舒服床垫又不丢脸
Hey, look, ain't no shame in wanting a big, comfy mattress, okay?
我懂
Look, I get it. I get it.
我的背开过三次刀
I've had three back operations, so I get it.
舒服才是王道 但现实很残酷
Comfort is king. But the facts are this...
我们俩像流浪汉 高级饭店一定
They ain't letting two rock eaters like me and you
不让我们进去
in some bougie-ass hotel.
我也不想住三流旅馆
And I ain't about that Holiday Inn life.
但我有个点子
But I got an idea.
想要睡高档床
If you want that bed,
就得玩很大
we gotta go big, or we gotta go home.
赞成吧？
Are you with me?
要不要参一咖？
Are you in or are you out?
我就当你是同意了
I'm going to take that as a yes.
欢迎光临富豪酒店
Welcome to the Grand Regal, sir.
你好
What up, cuz?
入住愉快
Enjoy your stay.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨 欢迎光临富豪酒店
Hi. Welcome to the Grand Regal, sir.
-嗨 抱歉 -嗨
- Oh, hi, sorry. - Hi.
嗨 您要入住吗？
Are you checking in?
对 麻烦了
Yes, please. I was...
希望还有空房
I was hoping, uh, that you might have
给我和我的导盲犬
a room for me and my little girl here.
我来看看
Oh, well, let me check on that.
她身上那是紫心勋章？
Oh, is that a purple heart? Was she wounded?
是啊…没错
Yes, she was. Oh.
感谢你为国效力
Thank you for your service. Oh.
进来时我就说吧
What did I say? Right when we walked in,
从古至今
I said that, "Never in history
只要是瞎掉的老兵 牵着英雄狗
has a blind veteran and his hero dog
进饭店 就能免费住
walked into a hotel and not gotten a free room."
为什么我会这样说？
And why did I say that?
为什么会这样？
Why did I say that happens every time?
没错
Oh, you're right.
自由 所以才会成功
Freedom. That is why that happens.
谁是天才？
Who's a genius?
你怎么了？
What... What's your... What's your deal?
你很热吗？
Why are you... Are you hot?
要喝水吗？
Do you want water? Huh?
脱掉背心 快起来
Let's get this vest off you. Come on, get up, get up.
快起来
Up! Come on.
老天 你臭死了
Oh, man, you stink.
狗狗
Okay, dog, here.
进来
Come on, let's get in.
水放好了
The water's fine.
过来 快进来
Come here. Come on. Let's go.
进来 过来
Let's go. Come here.
过来 快过来 快来泡澡
Come, come, come here. Get in the tub.
快来 快来
Come on, come on.
好吧
Okay.
你这小可爱
You good little nugget.
你真是个小可爱
Such a good little nugget.
快来 小甜心
Come on, little nugget.
快来 洗香香
Come on, now get in the nugget bath.
乖狗狗 快点
Good girl, come on.
快来 别怕
Come on. You're okay.
我会很温柔
I'll dip you like a nugget.
我不会把你淹死的
I don't want to kill you. Mmm-mmm.
小乖乖
Yeah, good girl. Good girl.
快点 快来
Good girl. Come on. Come on.
好耶 快点 过来
Come on, yeah! Get in. Come on, come on.
不 过来
No, no, no, come here.
过来 过来
Come here, come here, come here.
好舒服的热水澡
It's all nice and warm.
超舒服的热水澡 来享受吧
It's all nice and warm. Yes, it is. Yes, it is!
我们用了四颗沐浴球和沐浴盐
We went through four bath bombs, bath salts.
要不要打去预约SPA？
Should I call down to the spa and get us a slot down there
狗狗按摩？
for a doggy massage? Yeah?
虽然你不是
You're definitely not the girl
我想一起泡澡的妹子 但
I thought I'd be in the tub with, but, hey,
我也没得选
you know, I'll take what I can get at this point, I guess.
好 最后搓一下 来吧
All right. Last bit, all right? There we go.
等等 稍候 我来了
One second. One Minute. Hold on, I'm coming.
这就来
Yes, one second.
再等一下 来了
Um, one second, yes. Coming.
晚安 客房服务
Good evening, sir. Here with the room service.
-晚安 -晚安
- Good evening. - Oh, good evening.
-请问能进来吗？ -请进
- May I come in, please? - Yes, please.
我来扶门
All right. I can take the door.
一份肋眼三分熟
So we have one rib eye, medium rare,
一份印度咖哩饺
and one Indian samosas.
-还需要什么吗？-不了
- Anything else? - No.
-看起来棒呆了 -好吧
- Everything looks shipshape. - All right.
-感谢 -晚安
- Thank you very much. - Have a good evening.
狗狗 你该看看这家伙的脸
Hey, dog, you should see this guy's face.
不行
Hey! No!
下来 走开
Get off! Get off there!
别乱来 不要
Don't do it! Stop! No! No! You...
随便 反正我不在乎了 这是你的床
Okay. You know what? I didn't even care anyways.
我要出去了
That was your bed. 'Cause I'm going out.
我看起来像好野人吗？
Do I look like 200k a year or what?
看看你 坐在沙发上看起来真享受
Look at you, sitting on the couch, looking all cute.
干嘛不早点叫我
Why didn't you tell me all I had to do was just
打开电视 放你的
turn on the TV and put your greatest hits
杀敌精选 让你轻松一下
on of you mauling people, to get you to relax?
你这自恋狂
You narcissist.
难道你不爱印度菜？
What happened, no go on the Indian food?
我就说灵媒不可信
I told you, you can't trust psychics.
没事 我这有你喜欢的
But don't you worry. I got exactly what you want.
熟成带骨肥肉 准备开吃？
Dry-aged, marbled-on-the-bone beautifulness. Ready?
赏你 享用吧
Take it, savor it. Come on.
别怕 吃就对了
You don't have to be scared. Just take it out of my hand.
随便
Whatever.
别干蠢事
Do not do anything stupid.
干嘛？
What?
我才不要
Hell, no.
你想跟我来？
Oh, you think you're coming with me?
你以为我忘了我在波特兰有多衰？
Do you think I forgot about Portland?
不
No.
我死也不会忘记波特兰事件
I'll never forget about Portland. Ever.
回去躺着
Go lay back down.
你想要床
You asked for the bed,
我就给你床 去躺着
I got you the bed. Go lay down.
够了 别唉唉叫
Hey, no, no!
狗狗 别闹了
Hey, dog, no!
你这麻烦鬼
You're a first-class moron, you know that?
闻到没 狗狗？钱的味道
You smell that, girl? Money.
顺便恭喜
Congratulations, by the way.
-谢谢 -谢了
- Thank you. - Thanks.
-真抱歉 -抱歉
- Oh, I am so sorry. - Oh, sir, pardon me.
-你没事吧？-原来是布里格先生
- I'm... You okay? - Yes, Mr. Briggs.
-是的 -等等 我认得这声音
- Of course, yeah. - Wait, I know that voice.
-你哪位？-我是在柜台接待过您的
- Wait. Who's that? - Oh, we met at the front desk.
-对喔 -凯伦
- Oh, the... Yes. - Callan.
对喔 凯伦 柜台经理
Yes, Callan, the front desk angel.
我在找地方吃晚餐
I'm looking for a place to eat tonight.
有好餐厅推荐吗？
Any good recommendations?
内河码头有一间很棒的生蚝吧
Yes, there's a fantastic oyster bar down at the Embarcadero.
我爱生蚝
I love oysters.
很开胃
They really, you know, heighten the senses.
你几点下班？
What time do you get off?
7点
Uh, I'm off at 7:00.
7点 现在几点？
7:00? What time is it now?
不要 狗狗
Oh, no, no. No, no, no! Dog!
过来 狗狗 不要
Come here, dog! No, dog! Dog, no!
小心 抱歉
Watch out, watch out.
不要 狗狗 小心 抱歉
Dog! No, no, dog! No, dog!
不要 别动
Dog, dog, no, no, no! Move!
不要 放开
No, no! No, no, no, no!
把狗拉开
Get off! Get off.
不要
No!
我的天 慢慢来
Oh my god, take your time, take your time.
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
去找医生
Somebody get a doctor.
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不行
No!
你还好吗？冷静点
You all right? Take it easy, take it easy.
没事了 快起来
Okay. Here we go, here we go.
天哪 我看得见了
Oh, my God, I can... I can see.
我看见了 各位 我看见了
I can see. Guys, I can see!
你装成盲人
So you were impersonating a blind man
只是为了训练导盲犬？
as part of a seeing eye dog training exercise?
没错
Yep, that's right.
突然 你没料到
When suddenly, uh, unbeknownst to you,
你的狗挣脱了
um, your dog broke free from your grasp,
冲向大厅
sprinted the entire length of the lobby
-撞倒受害者 -对
- and muzzle struck the victim? - Correct.
你之前没看过这只狗…
And you've never seen this dog exhibit
表现出任何侵略举动？
any type of aggressive behavior before this?
对 她通常跟人很亲
Never. Never. She usually... She loves people.
她不会伤人 我想不通
It's out of her character. I really don't understand it.
-我也很震惊 -好
- Man, honestly, I'm in shock. - Uh-huh.
你还要补充什么吗？
Is there anything else you want to add?
那个人还好吧？
How is the guy? Is he all right?
-对 -他看起来没事
- Yeah. - He seemed okay.
早上我们会联络阿法德医生
Well, we're gonna be contacting Dr. Al-Farid in the morning.
要是他想提告 我们就会接管
He wants to press charges. We'll take it from there.
在那之前你继续蹲牢房
Until then, you just sit tight.
那只狗还好吗？
Cool, and the dog? Dog's okay?
你要联系动物管制队
We're gonna have to check with animal control on that one.
我什么时候能接走她？
Okay. So when do I get her back?
交保时？
Do I have to post bail or whatever?
交保？老兄 现在是周五晚上
Post bail? Buddy, it is Friday night.
法官周一早上才会进来
Judge is not back until Monday A.M.
我必须关住所有
And I am required to keep all suspects
仇恨犯罪的嫌犯
in possible hate crimes in my custody.
仇恨犯罪？
Hate crime?
少烦我 去问市政厅
Now, don't start with me. Take it to City Hall.
这和仇恨犯罪有什么关系？等一下
Who said anything about a hate crime? Wait, wait, wait.
等一下 让我...
Hold on a second. Okay. All right. Let me... Let me...
我就直说了
Let me level with you, man.
我是陆军游骑兵
Okay? I was an Army Ranger.
狗的主人是我过世的战友
That dog's handler was my buddy, and he passed.
我周日要把她带去亚利桑那州参加葬礼
I got to take her down to his funeral in Arizona on Sunday.
金星勋章的家属就靠我送她过去了
I got a Gold Star family that's just depending on me to get her there.
好吗 周一早上我保证会回来
All right? Now I'll be back here first thing Monday morning. I promise.
但今晚我得送她过去
I just... I got to get her and I got to go tonight.
你是陆军游骑兵？
You were an Army Ranger?
对
Yeah.
干嘛不早说？
Why the hell didn't you say so?
-抱歉 -何必浪费我
- I'm sorry. - Instead of puttin' me through
20分钟讲鬼话？
20 minutes of that Ray Charles bullshit, huh?
我是第202旅
I was in the 202nd.
老兄 跟你讲喔
Hey, buddy, I gotta tell you something.
我就直说了
And I gotta level with you.
你进入酒店大厅
You going into that hotel lobby, huh,
戴墨镜牵着狗
with that damn cane and those glasses, man.
你们陆军游骑兵有够带种
You Army Rangers, you've got balls of steel.
-不 那很蠢 -我是铁粉 没骗你
- No. It was stupid. - I'm a huge fan, seriously.
借问一下 你老实说
Hey, I gotta ask you something, on the real, on the real.
是你教唆那疯狗去咬中东佬吧？
You sent that little beast for that raghead, didn't ya?
啥？
What? Huh?
报复他们算计我们 对吧？
Get a little payback for what they took from us, right?
-对吧？-没有
- Right? - No. I... No,
-肯定没有 -少来
- definitely, I didn't do that. - Come on. Don't worry, man.
我口风很紧 我不会说出去
My lips are sealed. I'm not gonna say nothing.
我们宪兵很会保守秘密
And us 31 Alphas, we keep it tight. You know?
宪兵？
Alpha 31s?
我们会罩你们这些狠角色
Yeah, we looked out for you badasses real good.
守住大门 对吧？
Out by the front gate, right?
原来你是宪兵
Oh, you were an MP.
-正解 -果然
- Damn right. - Right.
你在暗示什么？
What are you implying?
我没暗示什么
Oh, no, no, I'm not implying anything.
你们宪兵的工作很辛苦
No, I mean, we... You MPs, man, you guys got a hard job.
所以我才睡得安心
I never slept better knowing that you guys
多亏你们守在警卫室 力挺我们
were out there at the guardhouse, on the wall, watching over us.
我欣赏你 兄弟
Yeah, I appreciate that, brother.
你不像我遇过的
Yeah, I appreciate it too that you're not like
其他游骑兵
all those other Army Rangers that I've met.
留着像摩西
You know, with the long beards
一样的山羊胡
flowing in the wind, like they were Moses?
按喇叭通过大门口 不亮证件
The car going right by the front gate, not showin' an ID,
对我们比中指 「感谢你为国效力」
flipping us off, "Thank you for your service."
你不是这种烂人吧？
Yeah, you're not one of those guys, are you?
我没干过这种事
No, I... No, no, no.
肯定没有
No, I definitely...
信你一回 知道我还相信什么？
You know what? I buy that. You know what else I buy?
白人士兵会命令狗攻击回教医生
White military guy sics his dog on a Muslim doctor
为美国蓝领阶级争口气
in the heart of woke-ing class America.
饶了我吧 让我带狗走人
Man, don't do this. Don't do this. Just let me get my dog and go.
狗又是你的啰
Oh, now it's your dog!
一夜好眠 贱人
Sleep tight, bitch.
布里格
Briggs?
起床啦 要列队指认了
Rise and shine. Line-up time.
转向左边
Step to the left.
还要指认？不就是我
Really? A line-up? It's like... It's me, right?
所有人转向右边
Everybody, step to your right.
这在干嘛？你们有养狗吗？
What are we doing? Did you guys even have dogs?
他看起来像猫奴
He seems like a cat guy.
-三号 安静 -不是我会是谁？
- Quiet, number three. - We all know it was me, right?
对 是他
Yes, it was him.
正面
Face forward.
是他
It's him.
了解 谢谢你
I got it. Thank you, sir.
听我说句话
Can I... Can I just, like... You know what?
这样吧 我供认好吗？
I'm just gonna confess. How about that?
三号 后退
Step back, number three.
听我说 我供认好不好？
No, I'm sorry. Can I confess? Is that, like, a thing?
我要吃午餐耶
Man, I've got lunch.
都是我的错
It was my fault. I don't...
我的狗只是受训完成使命
Look, my dog, she was just doing what she was trained to do.
很遗憾她的训练
And unfortunately, she was trained
就是攻击长得像阿法德医生的人
to attack guys that look like Dr. Al-Farid.
够了 三号
All right, that's enough, number three.
让他说 我想听
Wait, let him speak. I want to hear it.
她服役7年 8次派驻
She served seven years, eight deployments,
她救过无数的生命
but she did save more people than you can count.
我没有种族歧视
I'm not some racist piece of shit,
但我会全盘招供
but I'll confess to whatever it is that you want me to
一切听你们的
or do whatever you want me to,
只要有人保证
as long as someone promises me
周日把她送去参加葬礼
that they will get her to that funeral this Sunday.
一言为定？
Is that a deal that I can make?
这人真有事
Give me a break.
把他带过来
All right. Take him out of here.
-真假？不回应？-五分钟后下一组
- Really? Nothing. - Next group in five.
就这样？
That's it?
稍候 三号
Hold on, number three.
你装成盲人
So you impersonated a blind man
只是为了免费住酒店？
just to get a free hotel room?
是啊 确实
Uh, yeah, yeah, I did.
有个灵媒说我的狗她想...
Um, there was a psychic and she said that she wanted...
我的狗想睡舒服的床垫
My dog wanted a mat... Like, a comfy mattress.
别管了
And some... Never mind.
真是瞎扯
It's... It's insane.
是很瞎
It is insane.
就我来看 你也很瞎
And if you want my non-clinical opinion, so are you.
合情合理
Yeah, that's... That's fair.
但我想过更瞎的是
But the more I sit with it, it's even more insane to
我放下工作 特地从波士顿飞回来
leave my practice and fly back from Boston
只为起诉想把狗送去葬礼的老兵
just to prosecute a veteran trying to get his dog to a funeral.
只要答应我
Just promise, when it's all done,
事成后你会去看心理医生
you'll seek professional help.
遵命
I, uh... Yes, sir.
-慢走不送 -慢走
- Salaam. - Salaam.
还好吗 狗狗？
Hey, what's up, dog?
你好吗？
What's up? How're you doing?
看到你竟然会这么开心
Never thought I'd be this excited to see you.
她一直都这么喘吗？
Has she always panted so much?
对 她可能跟我一样怕热
Yeah, she runs... She runs hot, I guess, like me.
她不是怕热
She's not hot.
是创伤后的焦虑
That's anxiety. It comes from trauma.
我同事摸她耳朵
You know, she tried to bite my colleague
就差点被咬
when he lightly touched her on the ears.
好好照顾她或找个尽责的主人
Either take responsibility for her or find someone who will.
好 谢谢
Okay, thank you.
准备走人了？
You're ready to get out of here? Huh?
你的家当 快走
Your personal effects. Dismissed.
从我面前滚蛋
As in, get out of my face.
听到没？快滚出他面前
Did you hear the nice man? We should get out of his face.
来吧
Come on.
对了 警官
Oh, and, officer,
感谢你为国效力 贱人
thank you for your service, bitch.
走吧
Come on.
给我滚
Yeah, keep walking.
你看屁
What are you looking at?
知道何时跟进
♪♪ You got to know When to hold 'em ♪♪
何时跟进
♪♪ When to hold 'em ♪♪
知道何时放弃
♪♪ Know when to fold 'em ♪♪
何时放弃
♪♪ When to fold 'em ♪♪
知道何时走开
♪♪ Know when to walk away ♪♪
你满上相的
You're a very photogenic dog, you know that?
你是真英雄
You look like a hero.
你怎么没说你有个哥哥？
Why didn't you tell me you had a brother?
他就住在洛杉矶
And he lives in Los Angeles.
我和你有个共同点
We got something in common, me and you.
我在那座鬼城也有家人
I got family in that godforsaken city.
我们来做个约定
You know what? I'll make you a deal.
路上你不再搞怪
You don't do anything all psychotic on this trip,
时间也来得及 也许我们就去看他
and we make good time, we can go see him.
说定了？握手？
Maybe, okay? Is that a deal? Shake?
你在握手 居然
Shake. You got it.
成交
Okay, deal.
老天 算了
Jesus Christ. All right.
走吧 上去
All right, let's go.
知道何时跟进 知道何时放弃
♪♪ You've got to know When to hold 'em Know when to fold 'em ♪♪
知道何时走开 知道何时追加
♪♪ Know when to walk away And know when to run ♪♪
你坐在赌桌旁时绝对别数钱
♪♪ You never count your money When you're sittin' At the table ♪♪
牌局结束就有足够时间让你点收
♪♪ There'll be time enough for countin' When the dealin's done ♪♪
好 是时候了
Okay, game time.
如果我进去待太久
Look, if I'm spending too long in there,
你就放声哭
you have full permission to go psychotic,
我会出来
like usual, and I'll come out.
要不要穿外套？好像太假掰了
Jacket or no jacket? I feel like the jacket's too much.
我干嘛跟你讨论？
What am I doing, talking to you?
妈咪 「好奇猴乔治」结束了
Mommy, Curious George turned off.
宝贝
Okay, sweetie.
-等我过去 -好
- I'll be right there, okay? - Mmm-hmm.
妈咪 是谁？
Mommy, who's there?
只是妈咪的朋友
Uh, it's just one of Mommy's friends.
去我的房间
Go to my room,
待会我会准备好意大利面
I'll bring your pasta in a few minutes, okay?
好吧 你想要？给你
Well, you want it? You got it.
狗狗 我找过家人了 换你
Okay, dog, I tried my family, let's try yours.
怎样？
What?
你哥不在的话我们就走了
Look, if your brother ain't here,
别急 别急
we are definitely not waiting.
喔 喔 别
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. No, no, no, no, no.
-努努 -诺亚
- Nuke! - Hey, Noah.
抱歉不请自来
I'm sorry to barge in, man.
露露 是你吗？
Lulu, is that you?
我是莱利的战友
I'm one of Riley's old teammates,
我想让她见见她哥
and I figured, you know, I'd let her see her brother.
别摸她的耳朵
Watch her...
我懂
I know, I know.
她的耳朵很敏感 是吧 妹子？
She's sensitive on the ears, aren't you, girl?
乖狗狗 好耶
Good girl. Hey. Oh, yeah.
你还会爱的抱抱？认真？
You give hugs now, really?
露露是抱抱高手呢
Oh, yeah. Lulu gives the best hugs.
你们没抱过？
You've never had a Lulu hug?
我们没那么娘
No, we don't... We don't... We don't exactly hug.
你衣服穿中号还大号？
You a medium or a large?
你怕了？
Are you bitching out on me?
怕个屁
No, I'm not bitching out on you.
她这三天巴不得咬死我
She's been wanting to kill me for three days.
来吧 放马过来
Come on, let's go. Give it to me, come on, let's go.
保持冷静 玩个痛快 很好玩的
Stay calm. You're having fun. This is fun.
好玩？看到没
Oh, having fun? Just look at her.
她想杀了我
She wants to murder me.
-这才不好玩 -放轻松
-This isn't fun. -Relax.
-放轻松 -放马过来
- Relax. - Come on, come on.
放马过来 我们来玩玩
Come on, we'll make it fun.
好玩耶 来咬我啊
It's fun. Take a little piece.
你很想吧 你一定很想咬我
Take a little piece. I know you like it. I know you want it.
再说一次为什么要她咬？
Remind me again why we want her to bite.
她不懂战争 只是当做工作
She doesn't know what war is. For her, it's just work.
你要让她知道
You've got to show her that work can be fun again,
工作很好玩
nothing bad is going to happen, okay?
这样你们才会有默契
That's how you make a bond.
我们不需要默契
I don't need to make a bond, okay?
怎样？我不够好玩？
I just... What, am I not fun enough for you?
来啊
Come on.
给他玩下去 记得手举高一点
Just hold your arm up a bit higher.
举高了 快来咬
It's up, man. Take it. Come on, just get it.
-干得好 努努 -干得好
- Good boy, Nuke. Good boy! - Good boy.
教他这是用来磨牙
Let him know this is love, your chew toy,
只是玩玩
this is fun.
干得好 努努 干得好
Good boy, Nuke. Good boy.
你是说努努原本跟露露一样火爆？
So you're telling me that Nuke was just as messed up as Lulu.
我花半年每天训练他
I'd been working every day for six months
然后说服军方让我收养他
before I convinced the army to let me adopt him out.
当初我不敢确定
Thought we'd never get there.
现在我还敢让他当保姆
Now we trust Nuke to babysit.
孩子们 吃汉堡
Kids, burgers!
糟糕
Shit.
爹地 这掉到地上了？
Daddy, was this on the ground?
-没啦 -你说谎 我看到了
- No. - You're lying. I saw it fall.
宝贝 我接住了
Baby, I dropped it into my hand, okay?
不要紧啦
It's fine. You're fine.
周六还得遛小孩
Saturdays.
我连狗都顾不好
I can barely take care of the dogs.
你真是太神了
I don't know how you're doing all this.
我懂 我差点顾不了努努
Yeah, I get it. Nuke was about all I could handle,
但他不再苦撑时
but when he stopped struggling,
我也干脆不再苦撑了
that's when I realized maybe I could stop struggling too, you know?
你想莱利治得好露露吗？
Do you think Riley could've fixed Lulu?
让她继续参战绝对治不好
Not by keeping her in the fight, no.
你要懂得什么时候要重生 不然就等死
You gotta know when to hang 'em up or check out, I guess.
有时游骑兵就爱寻死
Well, sometimes Rangers just find a way to die, man.
帮我抱抱莱利的母亲
Give Riley's mom a big hug.
他们不常说话 但他很爱她
They didn't talk much, I know, but she meant a lot to him.
没问题 兄弟
Yeah, I will, man.
拜托 老天 该死 真是够啰
Oh, come on. No! Shit! You gotta be kidding me.
这一带的邻居还真友善
No, it's a real nice neighborhood you got here, man.
他们偷光我的东西 连莱利的背包
They got all my shit. They got Riley's shit.
和我的药都干走
They got my meds.
好样的
Well, that's good.
至少他父母还有狗牌
At least I can give his parents his dog tags.
好啊
Oh, good.
他们留下你的独角兽
They left your unicorn.
露露 露露
Lulu, Lulu, here.
去找
Seek.
露露 快去找
Yeah, Lulu, go, seek.
-干得好 -露露 去找
- Good boy. - Lulu, seek.
去找 去找
Seek, seek.
闻到了？
What's in here?
很好 很好
Oh, yeah. There we go. There we go.
干得好 努努 干得好
Good boy, Nuke. Good boy.
好 努努 过来
Okay, okay. Come on, Nuke.
努努 去找
Come, Nuke. Nuke. Seek.
我们应该找对方向了
I guess we're going in the right direction.
去找 去找
Seek, seek.
老婆 喂？
Yes, baby, yes.
水烧滚了
Put the water on, I'm sure it's boiling.
对 青酱好了
Yes, pesto is fine.
我只是带同事去晃晃
We're... I'm just showing my buddy the Boardwalk.
抱歉 蒂芬妮 我想去看看码头
Sorry, Tiffany, I just wanted to see the piers.
我们很快回来
Yes, okay. We'll be back soon, okay?
去找
Seek.
-努努 -嘿
- Nuke! - Oh, hey!
露露 快去找
Yeah, Lulu, go, go, seek.
去找
Seek, seek.
抓紧她 去找
Just don't let her go. Seek, Nuke.
去找
Seek.
去找 努努
Seek, Nuke.
去找...
Seek, seek, seek.
找出来 努努 找出来
Find it, Nuke. Find it.
去找
Seek.
给我闭嘴
Joe! Shut the hell up.
去找 去找
Seek, seek.
Seek. Seek.
去找 继续 去找
她找到了
Yeah, yeah, she found it, she found it.
干得好 努努
Good boy, Nuke.
没错
Yeah, this is it.
是我的东西 散了满地
Yeah, yeah, it's my shit. It's just everywhere.
这些毒虫可能正在吸我的头痛药
This crackhead's probably snorting my migraine meds right now.
莱利的东西都在
Yeah, most of Riley's shit's here.
她的本子也在
Her book's here.
搞什么鬼？这些是我的
Hey, what is this shit, man? This is private property.
-是吗？那是你的？ -对
- Oh, is it? That's yours? - Yeah.
-杰克森 走吧 -你叫做罗利兹？
- All right, Jackson, let's go. - Your name's Rodriguez?
我是美军老兵
Man, I'm a United States army veteran, man.
快脱掉
Yeah? Take it off right now.
-我才不脱 -你是哪一营的？
- I ain't taking off shit. - What battalion were you in?
那是机密
That's classified.
警告你 给我脱掉
Get it off! Get it off!
滚开 搞屁
Oh, goddamn, man.
可恶 我为国效力却得到这种回报
Hey, I serve my country, and this is the thanks I get?
我是战争英雄耶
I'm a war hero!
你没有药行吗？
You're gonna be all good without those meds?
我真该让她吃掉那个死小偷
I should have just let her eat that stolen valor piece of shit.
贫民窟的老兵是真是假很难说
You never know in places like that who served.
五年前你可能
And if you were here five years ago,
也会在码头下抓到我
you could have caught my ass under that pier,
情况也许更糟
and that would have been the best-case scenario.
但我们不会让自己沦落成这样
Yeah, but I didn't. 'Cause that bullshit ain't us.
是吗？
Yeah?
那莱利呢？
What about Riley?
莱利怎样？
他下床前要先吞三颗止痛剂
I mean, the dude couldn't get out of bed without popping three percs.
那是冠军早餐
Well, that's just the breakfast of champions,
他就是冠军
and he was a champion.
我数不清他打给我多少次
I can't tell you how many times he called me up,
我们喝茫闲聊我们想要的死法
we'd get shitfaced talking about how we were gonna check out.
听着 待在军队难免不好受
Look, man, we all deal with shit to stay in the game, okay?
所以就要永远留下？
So we're supposed to stay in it forever?
他说过要飚车飞进大峡谷
He used to talk about driving off the Grand Canyon at top speed,
结果他撞到树
but he drove himself into a tree instead.
我劝他说出来
I tried to get him to talk.
说出来？找治疗师说？
Talk, like what, to a therapist?
真是馊主意
That was a great idea.
不 找其他过来人说
No, to other guys who have gone through it,
甚至对上帝说也好
or even just to God.
上帝？
God?
你根本不懂莱利
Okay, you didn't know shit about Riley, all right?
听着 我不是耍白烂
Look, by God, I mean anything.
也能跟石头或鞋子说
Could be a rock, could be a shoe,
或是跟理发师说
could be his damn barber.
但我们迟早要找个对象说出来
But we all got to pick something at some point.
这个嘛
Well...
他没有说 也不会说
he didn't, and he won't.
所以就没啥好说了
So ain't no use bitching about it.
我们受训要挺身捍卫这个世界
You know, we trained to put the whole world on our back.
但到头来
At the end of the day,
最困难的是向朋友寻求帮助
the hardest thing was knocking on a friend's door.
掰 露露
Bye, Lulu.
帮我向你爹地问好
Say hi to your daddy for me.
我会为你们祈祷
I'll be praying for you guys.
我们会很好的
We're gonna be just fine.
过来
Come here.
孩子们
Hello, guys.
（诺加利斯 80公里）
希望明天你准备好了
I hope you're ready for this tomorrow,
你知道他们想看到什么吗？
because you know what they want, right?
他们想看见悲伤的战犬
They want the hero war dog all sad and stoic,
想念她的战争英雄老爹
just missing her hero war daddy.
他们不想看见什么？
What they definitely don't want...
他们可不乐见…
They definitely don't want you trying to eat everybody
护旗队一鸣枪就被你咬
as soon as the color guard starts firing their salute.
但他们并不了解你
Now, they... They don't know you. That's for damn sure.
他们不明白当上英雄的代价
They don't know what it takes to be a hero.
还有你成为英雄狗的经历
The things you've done to be a hero dog.
要是他们知道真相
If they knew the truth,
包准会吓到挫屎
it would scare the living shit out of them.
我退役时
You know, when I got out,
你爹地给我一片木板
your daddy gave me this shitty piece of plywood
上面刻着「谢谢」两字
with the word "Thanks" carved in it.
似乎多说无益了
It's like, what else do you say to somebody
大家都曾一起出生入死
that you experience what we experienced together?
你有在听吗？
You even listening to me?
我竟然跟狗说心事
Just talking to a dog.
搞什么？
What is that?
没这么衰吧
No. No, no.
帮帮忙
No, no. Come on.
别在这时候出包
Don't you do this to me now.
糟糕
No.
该死
Okay...
当然没讯号
Of course, there's no service.
怎么会有讯号
Why would we have service?
别乱跑
Hey, hey, hey.
有人吗？
Hello?
别急
Hey.
真是的
Come on.
我们得走了
All right, we got to go.
来吧 我们得走了
Come on. We're moving on.
喔 喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
别慌 别慌
Hey, hey, no.
别乱跑 冷静
No. Chill out.
别慌 别慌
Hey. Hey, hey!
不要怕 别紧张
No! Stop! Relax!
没事 只是打雷和
Look, stop. It's just thunder.
大雨 我们要走了 别怕
It's just a thunderstorm. We gotta... Stop.
冷静下来
Calm down. Stop!
要不要走？那就快点
All right, you want to go? Come on. Come on, then.
快点 别闹脾气了
Come on, you're not gonna do shit.
我们快走
Come on, then, let's go!
你这小孬孬
Such a coward.
没事 我不会逼你出去
Easy. I'm not gonna make you go out there, okay?
我们冷静一下吧
How about we just chill out for a little while?
放轻松
Relax.
别怕
Hey, it's okay.
只是打雷和闪电
It's just thunder and a little lightning.
这样吧 我来想办法
You know what? How about this? Let me see if I can
转移注意力
give us a little something to take our mind off.
脚掌交叉求好运 也许管用
Cross your paws. Let's see if this thing works.
你想干嘛？
What do you feel like?
你喜欢旧金山吧？
Who doesn't like San Francisco?
想要看你的精选？
You want to watch your greatest hits,
还是看《实习医生》？
or do you wanna watch... Wanna watch Grey's?
我来放《实习医生》好了
I'm gonna go with Grey's.
（露露最爱的《实习医生》集数）
看 管用
It works.
我们舒服休息一下
We're just gonna rest,
放轻松
we're gonna get a little cozy, relax.
看个垃圾节目
Watch a little trash TV.
吃个零食 看垃圾节目一定要配零食
A little snack 'cause you can't watch trash TV without a snack.
（爆米花）
怎样？
What?
你也想吃？
Oh, you want some?
是不是 我们吵完多麻吉
Look at that. Who knew you just needed to have a fight to get along?
你爹地念过情书给你听吗？
Did Latin Shakespeare ever, like, read you his love letters?
有些不错
Some pretty good ones in there.
我念给你听
Let's see.
就这封了
What about...
好了
Okay.
「我瞬间醒来」「我看到你被泥土覆盖」
"I woke for an instant when I saw you covered in dirt.
「你曾中弹」
You've taken bullets before.
「但这次最严重」
This was the worst.
「我仍内疚不已」
The guilt still haunts me.
「我必须承认」
I'm not going to lie,
「但那晚你的壮举」
but I know you did what you did that night,
「救了所有弟兄的生命」
so none of your brothers had to die."
不是盖的
It's pretty good.
「他们把你带走时」
"When they took you away,
「我相信我们没时间了」
I was sure we'd run out of time
「我当下心里有数 狗狗」
and that's when it hit me, girl,
「我不是你的驯犬师」
I was never your handler.
「我永远是你的主人」
That you were actually mine.
「你的兄弟 莱利」
Your brother, Riley."
你跟卡瑞睡了？
You slept with Corrine?
对
Yeah.
哈？有够瞎的
What? Okay.
你居然爱看这种垃圾
I cannot believe you actually like this trash.
超假掰
Unreal.
好 太阳出来
All right, the sun's up.
该走了
It's time.
我们的机会渺茫
There is about zero chance of us making it
6小时内要赶往100公里外的地点
a hundred clicks in six hours
而且手机没讯号又没车
with no cell phone service or ride.
但据我所知
But, hey, last time I checked,
游骑兵的字典里没有放弃
"surrender" is not a Ranger word.
管你怎么想 我要参加葬礼
I don't know about you, but I got a funeral to go to.
走吧
Come on.
（谢谢）
走吧
Come on.
保佑我的心 保佑我的灵魂
♪♪ Bless my heart Bless my soul ♪♪
没想过我能活到22岁
♪♪ Didn't think I'd make it To 22 years old ♪♪
天上一定有个人说
♪♪ There must be Someone up above ♪♪
「加油 布兰妮」
♪♪ Saying "Come on, Brittany You got to come on up!" ♪♪
你要撑下去
♪♪ You got to hold on ♪♪
♪♪ Hey, you got to hold on ♪♪
停下 拜托 停下
Hey, hey, hey, please, please. Come on.
停下 拜托停车 停车
Come on, please, please. Come on! Man.
也保佑你的心灵
♪♪ So, bless my heart And bless yours too ♪♪
我不知何去何从
♪♪ I don't know Where I'm gonna go, don't what I'm gonna do ♪♪
天上一定有个人说
♪♪ Must be somebody up above ♪♪
「加油 布兰妮 你要加把劲」
♪♪ Saying "Come on, Brittany You got to come on up!" ♪♪
你要撑下去
♪♪ You got to hold on ♪♪
♪♪ Yeah, you got to hold on ♪♪
你要撑下去
♪♪ Yeah, you got to wait! ♪♪
♪♪ Yeah, you got to wait ♪♪
但我不想等待
♪♪ But I don't wanna wait ♪♪
你一定要等待
♪♪ Yeah, you got to wait ♪♪
但我不想等待
♪♪ But I don't wanna wait ♪♪
我不想等待
♪♪ I don't wanna wait ♪♪
我们会赶上的 走吧
We're gonna make it. Come on.
走吧
Come on.
我们快到了
Almost there.
（公墓）
你会看起来很体面
You're gonna look great.
你看起来会像
You're gonna look like a hero,
莱利心中的英雄
just like Riley would've wanted.
好了
Okay.
知道莱利还喜欢什么？
You know what else Riley would've liked?
你不乱咬人 最好不要
You not to bite anybody, so maybe just don't do that.
过来
Come on.
接受主的祝福
Receive the Lord's blessings.
愿主祝福你和看顾你
May the Lord bless you and watch over you.
愿你使祂的脸照亮所有人
May He make His face to shine upon each and every one of you
对祂感恩
and be gracious to you.
愿祂慈爱地看你
May He look lovingly on you
赐你和平
and grant you peace.
愿祂保佑你的小孩和家人
May He bless your children and your families...
让他们明白爱和幸福
that they may know love and happiness.
愿你明白那种深情
May you know that love deeply.
愿爱永远与你同在
And may He always be with you.
我们不该哀悼…
We should not grieve for...
露露
Lulu.
冷静 没事的
Come on. It's okay.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
没事的
No, no, no. It's okay.
没事
Okay, fine, all right.
好了 放心去吧
Okay, it's okay, go.
没关系
It's okay.
让我们欢送已故的挚爱兄弟
So let us rejoice for our dearly departed brother.
他伫立在最后岗位
For he has stood his last watch,
现在他最终要离去
and he's now on his final deployment.
因父 及子 及圣神之名 阿们
In the name of the Father and the Son and the Holy Spirit. Amen.
列队 举枪
Detail. Port Arms.
半面向右转
Half right, face.
装空包弹 上膛
With blank ammunition, load!
预备
Ready!
瞄向天空 开枪
Aim! Fire!
别紧张
Easy.
瞄向天空
Aim!
开枪
Fire!
-别紧张 -瞄准 开枪
- You're okay, you're okay. - Aim! Fire!
-预备 -别紧张
- Ready... - You're okay, you're okay.
停火
Cease fire!
重置 放下
Present Arms!
你没事的
You're okay. You're okay.
谨代表美国总统
On behalf of the President of the United States,
美国陆军及感恩的国家
the United States Army, and a grateful nation.
谢谢
Thanks.
好
All right.
过来 走吧
Come on, let's go.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
明早会如期送她过去
Yep. Still on schedule to drop her off
我会打给安全中心
First thing in the A.M.
我会跟他们说等你的电话
All right, I'll tell him to expect your call.
上尉 谢谢你打电话
Hey, and, Captain, thank you for making this call.
-感谢 -没问题 兄弟
- I really appreciate it. - You got it, brother.
还有一件事
Oh, uh, one more thing.
听着 她有进步
Look, she's... She's doing a lot better.
这只狗不一样了
I mean, she's a completely different dog now.
也许我们能跟基地人员
I don't know, maybe there's someone on base
说些好话
that one of us could talk to.
布里格 那由不得我们
Briggs, you know that's not up to us.
-就别管了 -好吧
- Just get it done. - Yeah.
祝好运 布里格
Good luck over there, Briggs.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
好
All right.
要走了
Let's go, let's go.
去尽个笨义务吧
Let's go do something stupid.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
你想去那里吗？
You wanna go out there?
你想去找点乐子吗？
You see something you wanna go get?
你自由了 快去
You're free, go.
去吧 我不会阻止你
Go for it. I ain't gonna try to stop you.
听到没？
You hear me? Hey.
快走
Go.
走开
Get out.
快走
Go, come on. No. Hey.
我不是在跟你玩
No, I'm not trying to tell you to do tricks, kid. No.
快走
Get. Go.
快点 还不快走
Hey. Hey.
走 去吧
Now. Come on. Come on.
你还在状况外吧 狗狗？
You got no idea, do you, dog?
我没事
I'm okay.
I'm okay, girl.
别担心
I'm all right.
我没事 我没事
I'm okay. I'm okay.
我没事了
I'm okay.
你很棒
You're okay.
好 露露 走吧
All right, Lulu, come on.
（美国陆军 白沙飞弹靶场）
-证件 先生 -好
- ID, sir? - Yeah.
证件过期 早该作废了
Your army ID has expired.
知道啦 我只是把狗送来
You're required by law to dispose... Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got you.
要交给利瓦伊兹下士
Uh, I'm just dropping off the dog, man, uh, to a Corporal Levitz.
利瓦伊兹
Hey, Levitz!
帮个忙 车停旁边
Do me a favor, park right here.
好
Yeah.
老兄 你们游骑兵真是办事不力
Shit, man. You Rangers ever hear of callin'?
我在大太阳底下等了一小时
I've been out here cooking my ass off for an hour.
还好吧
It could be worse.
等一下又不会死人
You could be actually working.
听说她很凶暴
All right, man. I hear she's a real killer,
一定要把她的嘴套戴好
so just make sure you muzzle her up good, okay?
好
Yeah.
没事
Don't worry.
她不会惹麻烦的
She ain't gonna be a problem.
是吧？
Are you, girl?
最后一次戴好吗？最后一次
Last time, okay? Last time.
再戴一次就好
Just gonna put it on one more time.
兄弟 她变得温驯多了
Hey, man, she's been doing a lot better.
一定要请兽医
So just make sure the vet techs, you know,
重新鉴定她 给她一个机会
reevaluate her, give her a chance.
好 他们有自己的程序
Yeah, yeah, they got their protocol.
你听到了 说到做到
You heard me. Make sure.
交接完 你会打给琼斯上尉吧？
So as soon as we're done here, you're gonna call Captain Jones, yeah?
上头有吩咐
That's what they're telling me.
干嘛 你想惹毛她吗？
What are you... Look, man, are you trying to piss her off?
你会没事的 好吗？
All right. You're gonna be okay, all right?
好了 我没时间 走吧
Come on, man, I ain't got all day, let's go.
我套住一下就好
I'm just gonna put this on you.
给他们好看
Give 'em hell.
走吧 快点
All right, let's go.
不行 不行
Oh. No, no, no, no, no.
别想了
Come on.
别冲动
God. Easy, easy, easy, easy.
等等 等等
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
嗨 嗨 没事
Hi, hi, hi. No. It's fine. It's fine.
我的错
My bad.
我应该让她穿上背心
I should have... You know what, I should have put a vest on her.
她穿背心会比较听话
She listens more when the vest is on.
这妹子很有个性
You know girls and their fashion.
很快回来 上车
I'll be right back. Up!
先生 你忘记你的证件
Sir, you forgot your ID.
送你好了
Uh, you know what, man, why don't you keep it?
感谢你为国效力
Thank you for your service.
那狗呢？
Hey, man, what about the dog?
玩什么把戏？看什么看？
What are you... What are you looking at?
别害我爆哭
Let's not make this all emotional, okay?
亲爱的露露
Dear Lulu,
我今天向军方拿了收养文件
I got the adoption papers from the army today.
莱利会很骄傲
Riley would be so proud.
也许你和我都让他骄傲
Maybe even of both of us.
听着 我不会写诗
Look, I'm no good at this poem stuff,
所以我直接讲重点
so I'll just get to the damn point.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢让我重生
Thanks for saving my life.
（露露 《爱自己》）
道路像迎宾地毯开展
♪♪ Well the road rolls out Like a welcome mat ♪♪
通往比我们所在更好的地方
♪♪ To a better place Than the one we're at ♪♪
我毫无计划
♪♪ And I ain't got No kinda plan ♪♪
但我已走遍这个城镇
♪♪ But I've had All of this town I can stand ♪♪
我在海岸边有朋友
♪♪ And I got friends Out on the coast ♪♪
我们能跳入水中 看看漂流物
♪♪ We can jump in the water And see what floats ♪♪
我们未雨绸缪
♪♪ We've been saving For a rainy day ♪♪
一起战胜风暴 继续前进
♪♪ Let's beat the storm And be on our way ♪♪
我不在乎 我们四处为家
♪♪ It don't matter to me Wherever we are Is where I wanna be ♪♪
亲爱的 人生就这一次
♪♪ And, honey For once in our life ♪♪
让我们把握机会冒险尝试
♪♪ Let's take our chances And roll the dice ♪♪
我来当你的幸运符
♪♪ I can be your lucky penny ♪♪
你能当我的四叶草 重新来过
♪♪ You can be My four-leaf clover Starting over ♪♪
日子也许不好过
♪♪ This might not Be an easy time ♪♪
跋山涉水度难关
♪♪ There's rivers to cross And hills to climb ♪♪
有些白昼令人崩溃
♪♪ Some days We might fall apart ♪♪
有些夜晚又黑又冷
♪♪ And some nights Might feel cold and dark ♪♪
没有赢家怕失败
♪♪ When nobody wins Afraid of losing ♪♪
艰难路才值得选
♪♪ And the hard roads are The ones worth choosing ♪♪
有天我们会回眸一笑
♪♪ Some day we'll Look back and smile ♪♪
明白每哩路都值得走
♪♪ And know it was Worth every mile ♪♪
我不在乎 我们四处为家
♪♪ It don't matter to me Wherever we are Is where I wanna be ♪♪
亲爱的 人生就这一次
♪♪ And, honey For once in our life ♪♪
让我们把握机会冒险尝试
♪♪ Let's take our chances And roll the dice ♪♪
我来当你的幸运符 你能当我的四叶草
♪♪ I can be your lucky penny You can be My four-leaf clover ♪♪
重新来过
♪♪ Starting over ♪♪
（谨以本片纪念露露）